<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="stories_content2">

<item>Definition of violence against women Violence against women is intentional, violent behavior directed towards women, and it takes many forms, whether moral or physical, and according to the definition of the United Nations, violence against women is the behavior practiced against women and is driven by sexual nervousness, which leads to suffering and harm that affects women in the physical, psychological and sexual aspects, The threat in any way, deprivation, and restricting the freedom of women in their private or public lives is a practice of violence against women. Violence against women is a clear and explicit violation of human rights; It prevents her from enjoying her full rights, and it has serious consequences that not only affect women, but affect the entire society. Because of its serious social and economic implications. It is worth noting that violence against women does not define a specific culture, religion, country or social class, but rather is a general phenomenon.
</item>

    <item>Physical violence: Physical violence is one of the most prevalent types of violence against women, and this type of violence includes any physical harm to women, whether it is a beating or using a machine, as this entails significant health and psychological risks to the victim, and may sometimes cause the death of the victim As a result of excessive force and severe beatings.
</item>
    <item>Psychological violence: It is the type that most affects a womans mental health, and it can be verbal or non-verbal violence, where verbal violence is by insulting women with vulgar words and wounding their dignity in front of others, as well as
Psychological violence is by mocking and belittling it and not showing any interest in it.</item>
    <item> Sexual violence: This violence takes many forms, including sexual harassment or any sexual threat, or any relationship
It is forced or coerced.</item>
    <item>Economic violence: This type of violence is represented by controlling and controlling the material resources that a woman deserves in order to humiliate her, and may be by depriving her or forcing her to work, or taking her right from inheritance.</item>
</string-array>

</resources>